(All(repeatedly):)Refresh... Refresh...
(Sheldon:)-Refresh.
-Refresh.
Refresh. It's been ten minutes!
We're running out of time.
(Penny:)To be cool? Yeah.
I did it! I did it!
I'm in the queue!
(Sheldon:)And they say firefighters
are the real heroes.
(Raj:)What number in line are you?
(Leonard:)-Fifteen...
-Great!
-...thousand, 211.
-Damn!
(Raj:)They only have Thursday
and Sunday passes left.
(Howard:)-Really?
-Thursday's gone. Just Sunday left.
Sunday's the worst!
(Sheldon:)Everybody's leaving,
most of the good panels are over,
(Sheldon:)and the only T-shirts
they have left are small and XXXXL.
(Leonard:)-Sunday's gone.
-Not Sunday! I love Sunday!
(Raj:)So that's it?
Everything's sold cut?
(Penny:)Yeah.